hello
there was one wing okay so we got a
little craw
we're gonna be talking about three
things today bro
I might stream on Twitch later today so
we're gonna be exploring EOS today no
scopes this weekend
no I guess somewhere just sure though I
went hiking shop.com down I of course I
know
so first thing we're gonna do is we're
gonna look at some way mo advertising
um blame Orion's I believe is like a
Saturday morning we were all going to a
friend's house and we drove by a
residential neighborhood it was with
kids families around attention to car I
noticed has stopped all the sudden I was
like why but Shaw had run out from okay
so if you guys walk that's disgusting
this this this whole presentation is
absolutely disgusting
way mo should be ashamed of themselves
like this is the corn those two and stop
faster than I could never reacted what's
surprising is the weight of the car
seats
[Music]
those aren't users those are actors yeah
exactly
um this is not a way to present
technology this is and and this shows
the difference kind of in how maybe us
and Tesla and companies like way mo view
self-driving cars um you know just I
want you to think about the kind of
world those people are gonna create so
maybe maybe maybe um justjust justjust
just be aware when you're when you're
watching particularly I find way mo to
be the most disgusting in this matter
and it's sad because they do have good
technology look I understand when the
company like drive that AI does this
because they don't have anything else
but Wayne well has a lot to offer know
that PO I mean again the few hundred
users almost are literally actors right
it's sad because way mo has good
technology there's no reason they have
to do this they don't this isn't this
isn't making people you know excited or
more comfortable with self-driving cars
this is disgusting and everybody sees it
I know maybe this is a lot of complaints
about the media these days okay so
that's that's that's the way Moab
yeah the users have nd
they're not they're practically actors
right
I felt like our piece of equipment okay
in some way you have to kind of feel a
little bad for them because they're very
constrained by the Google brand people
Google works very very hard on their
brand like making sure oh it's googly
right and I think that what made Google
good in the past that technology which
they do have great technology has fallen
by the wayside and not just Google but
also in Weibo so I find me I find the
way more advertising to be particularly
repulsive cool so that's the way
[Music]
I notice how we're still use the word
were a worry worry worry worry
what come on okay uh we should talk
about this uber drivers watching The
Voice moments before fatal Tempe crash
up guys there are no self-driving cars
no software and cars are real all cars
are still level to make sure to pay
attention at all times well then that's
all we'll say about that um the other
thing that I wanted to look at was
Yandex released a video this is just
read it self-driving cars it's here I
don't know how it's got a million views
this is literally every single one of
the scenes in this video I think open
pilot would do a better job in their car
like this is over violent effectively
they could have literally run open pilot
on this car from his Drive and would
have done just as well I think it's I
think it's pretty oh no I can't tell ya
but I mean this is literally you know go
go to chef they come to the I by any odd
install up and pilot on it and you will
literally get dis this way no car but
you know okay
well let's let's at least talk about how
I think I mean this is just people who
are behind but I think this is at least
this tastes right like this is much like
our Drive you right this is nothing like
way more at least this is uh this is
tasteful it's nice you know everyone
likes to see nice time five studios and
people driving but it is it may be
edited out all the disengagement some
yes so just something to be aware of
they talk about how it's 99% in
autonomous mode that doesn't really mean
anything
um when 99% autonomous mode would mean
they do have a huge screen that does a
big Russian screen no but um 99 percent
doesn't mean anything because it's not
it works on 99% of roads you have to be
always be very careful when you're
looking at probabilities is actually a
great paper that just came out about the
Drake Equation they talk about the
difference between point estimators and
range estimators and how that could come
up with massively different results for
the Drake Equation which I thought was
really cool you guys can check out that
paper I did some some favorite physics
guys name I can't remember I should I
should shout it out properly no no
there's new dissolving the Fermi paradox
are you okay Sandberg and Drexler and I
never heard
before but um they can't use GPS because
it's not reliable in Russia I mean
Russia has their own GPS is called
GLONASS and to tell our reliable in
Russia though GLONASS a little thing
about GLONASS GPS is narrowband
of GLONASS is wideband and it makes it
much harder to do precise very precise
stuff because the ionosphere has
different delay times for different
frequencies for GPS all the GPS
satellites at least the l1 GPS
satellites are all don't have a actually
say that so cool I think GPS does work
pretty well in Russia we have pretty
good global coverage you can also
probably get the BAE do satellites
bay-do uses the same frequency as GPS
beta was the Chinese GPS but using
mirrors for peripheral vision um no I
don't think that's a particularly good
idea where would I put the mirrors know
you'll see what the solution is it's
probably what you expect in order to get
to anything that requires that it's more
cameras but guys a lot of the
disengagement sweer still getting an
open pilot our biggest source of
disengagement Snow's cuttings we're
gonna announce some big stuff about how
we're gonna try to really drive
disengagement down but our biggest
source of disengage now is cutting and
there are visible cuttings so open pilot
only detects the cars in front of you
using the radar it doesn't use the
camera it uses the camera for fusion
confirmation if the radar detects a
stopped object this is I mean you see
the auto pilot cars you see all the time
they crash into things in front of them
and this is the same bug because you
can't just trust and we'll get to why we
don't use lidar in a minute you can't
just trust the radar because sometimes
radars will detect like manhole covers
or bridges as stopped cars and if you
guys in the Toyota sometime will
experience false braking so it's a
trade-off right a false positive means
hard braking but a true positive means
you crash into something right so you
want to get hit from the front of the
back so you got it you got to kind of
tune these things it's a no-win scenario
the aschen marui why don't we use
lighter so um the problem thank you
thank you
the problem with lidar is twofold one
it's very expensive you if you what was
show me what lidar you can buy today
that's reasonably priced and you'll
point I don't look I can buy the slider
for five hundred dollars but just
because they're both called lidar it's
nothing like the kind of lidar you'll
find on lame-o cars so you say twelve
thousand which light are you talking
about and let me also remind you at
twelve thousand you can for twelve
thousand dollars you can buy twelve Eon
giraffe panda combinations that's even
midnight black eons
maybe maybe normally on grey panda
giraffe with international shipping so
you can buy twelve exactly there are
certain control changes that can address
that let them yeah vision mark radar
yeah those things we can do better there
why can't lie to our be made in mass
scale for much cheaper so there's no
fundamental reason that it can't but no
companies have done it yet all right so
we're not gonna spin up the comma a I
lied our division and try to make lidar
it makes no sense
Oster twelve thousand dollars is still
too much money now so there's that
aspect to it um you know could you make
ladders cheaper yeah someone probably
well and then at that point we can we
can reevaluate our usage of lidar I'll
show you a Bosch radar image not sure
exactly we mean by that ladder will be
cheap is still five thousand is still
too much and then there's also a
question of I'm not sure what you think
lighter gets you right lidar doesn't
tell you how to drive a car all lidar
gives you is a depth based point cloud
of an environment you can do very
similar things today using even a single
camera combined with deep learning
obviously you can use let's find mono
cam depth that's right yeah that's why I
mean by the $500 liners that aren't
really what you
what um so this one good this one's old
there's very good ones now let me find
the cityscapes
yep tonight
so my point is lidar is pretty similar
to a camera plus a depth now we used to
troll that we were going to put make a
box with a GPU and a camera and then
sell it as a lidar so you see the depths
there that are being returned as I
believe this is mono cabin might be
stereo cabinets it's all very similar
yeah like you can infer depth this depth
ground truth was probably taken with a
liner and this is uh without the liner
you see this is even picking up on some
things that are not in the ground truth
like that tree over there oh yeah I'm
not really sure why what you think
you're gonna get with a liner
I mean the more expensive liners do with
higher resolutions they still don't have
resolutions that even come close to
cameras so we have a thirty thousand
dollar lidar at , it's a thirty two line
lidar and it spins and it takes I think
about a hundred thousand points per
second so for comparison we're running
the camera on your eon at one megapixel
well actually three megapixels to be
precise we're really running into three
megapixels is how we do the RGB things
but three megapixels it runs at 20 Hertz
so that's 60 million data points we're
getting 60 million data points instead
of a hundred thousand from lidar so
you're getting six hundred times more
data with the EON than you do with even
a thirty thousand dollar lidar so wider
is one of these things again is this way
Mo's advertising why does everybody
think like lidar is important it's it's
really not I'm now we're lidar will do a
great job is in localization you can
localize yourself very precisely and
light our maps with a lie are this is
like the entire strategy of cruise
automation for example absolute
automation has built their core
technology was a very precise lidar slam
they've built a ladder map of San
Francisco and then they can localize
themselves in it
any more questions this is Sunday
sculpey where we answer your questions
you ask them we answer them why do
people want to ask about we can also go
through self-driving cars and see what
else oh well
so I mean
Wow Volvo premises self-driving 2021
xc90 you can ask guys
whenever you see stories like this the
engineers probably were not asked right
so um how many I is a company built by
engineers run by engineers controlled by
engineers this is a marketing story in a
lot of companies you have a structure
that looks something like this we can
talk a little bit about maps in about
peripheral vision so I mean you already
know what the solution to peripheral
vision is right the solution to
peripheral vision is more cameras of
course so you want to see out the side
of the car long you put a camera on the
side of the car right so most companies
are structured vaguely like this right
so you have really companies are run by
our business men Duvall has a tweet he
talks about how there is no such skill
is business this is true there is no
such thing as business business right
looks like business Wow um but yeah and
then you have engineer over here and you
have PR over here right so when they say
2020 probably what happened is the
business people make up 2021 and they
tell both the PR people this and the
engineers this right so what happens
then is the PR people are like okay well
we'll push this story follow will have
an XD 90 you can sleep in by 2021 and
the engineers are wait a second we can
try I mean I don't know if we can I
don't know if we can right so whenever
you see stories like that they're
complete garbage now I you know really
who the fault who I blame for for this
for this disaster fire is the media all
right so PR doesn't exist in a vacuum
I think we can find that that stories on
SEANET am i right
so let's take a look at it you know they
don't even want you to read the article
past the uh that's the title but let's
take a look here okay Volvo senior vice
president oh okay so this is the
business people right yeah see that is
trash right like this is this is a
complete trash article right this is
practically a press release from the
company so you know just just just
things to be aware of that this
shouldn't be tolerated in the world
anymore I hope that I mean I hope that
especially you know after after you know
what's happened politically people need
to stand up in this country and be like
wait a second
the media is bullshit um the media is
tons of it's just that's just total
bullshit right that's nothing that's a
journalism that's a press release um
pew news right I am PewDiePie Kenny by
saying the same stuff and it's it's
great you know we have we have people
like that calling out the bullshit um so
yeah the fruitful vision you guys know
what the solution is you put eyes on the
side of the car no I don't doubt their
desire it's my desire that I doubt
Boston when the prints come pretty well
[Music]
mapping is our graphic guys been on
vacation for the last weeks it's been
zero progress in battle sorry guys I'll
tell you the truth
you know I'm a always telling the truth
okay
will Tesla make it yes yes um in fact
here's another thing here's another
thing to think about with respect to
Tesla when you ask a question like will
Tesla make it why do you think that they
might not oh we got the car past these
presentations great big props to
Carpathia for that by the way we can we
can dissect a little bit of that in a
minute but when you hear that Tesla
might not make it
oh there was a there was a seeking out
the article that talks about yeah okay
okay okay okay Tesla is growing
massively if you have growth growth is
better than profit right I'm thinking
about it like this if you could make 1
million dollars profit this year or you
can lose 5 million dollars but make 10
million dollars next year you're much
better off I mean think about it at the
end of the at the end of the two years
right at the end of the two years let's
say gonna make a million dollars a year
if you sacrifice cars the profitability
of two million versus at the end of two
years you have five million um so when
you're in business you want to be
thinking long term now if when you have
when you're having long mosque
I mean he's thinking very long term
right here's what I would worry about
Tesla worried about Tesla when nobody
wants to buy their cars if the demand
side of Tesla dries up then I would be
concerned about Tesla's a company right
if everyone is like well I'm not buying
model threes I'm not buying Model T's
but as far as I can tell legitimately
there still is lines I mean let's see
there's some I got 300,000 people in
line for the model 3 it's like a sizable
percentage of the population of San
Francisco right um whatever three people
in San Francisco like from a demand
perspective um Tesla's crushing a and
that's really all you have to look at
the other thing too is people who are
said well you know you want promised
with all these big things he does and he
promises timelines that I aren't really
mad but but but but those timelines are
least I mean talk about a company run by
an engineer right when Ilan gives his
two-year timeline he's not lying to you
it's not the way Volvo gives a timeline
like Volvo is straight up that's
completely disconnected from reality
Elon really believes it will be done in
two years right Vermeulen perspective
now you can fault him maybe for not you
know being able to predict his own his
own you know the stuff do I believe the
employee sabotage story again it's so
filtered by the media what do you mean
do I believe it yes I believe that there
was an employee sabotage is perhaps a
strong word but I believe that he was
out to get Tesla and was working at
Tesla and was fired I think that that's
the whole story right um Tesla's issue
is about what cost i retweeted it there
was a good article that explains how
much people have to lose by Tesla's
success I don't make predictions like
that I'm never gonna there's no stupid
prediction to make that when the
disengagement is go to zero right but
when do I think their car you could nap
it will come out well I'll tell you open
pilot has X number dis engagements when
we get X down below threshold of human
dis engagements will tell you you can
take a nap right you can take a nap in
any car today
you could go buy a 92 you know Toyota
Celica and take a nap in it I mean you
might die but you know right I'll cost
to manufacture Tesla cars it's not high
it's it's really Tesla's we could talk
about where cost comes from in the
automotive sector why cars are expensive
I think that uh you're Gary you're
overestimating this what type of
hardware you process everything on a GPU
German and also that's the other thing
too like car you can take a nap in you
could take a nap in any car this is this
is another thing that just kills me
about like the media and public
discourse
please be precise in your language like
like like have precision when you speak
what do you mean by that do you mean a
car where the manufacturer will take
liability when it's driving that's a
whole different thing please say that
that's real that's something that means
something not a car you can take a nap
it I've taken a nap at all my cars
they're just worried I was moving all
right are you saying you're gonna add a
GPU in the car it's even think it's just
ignorance um no no one comes everyone
fire over sabotage the past ml guys
weren't fired but but more for you know
you see what's possible now that you've
seen the good model is location D on the
phone blocked by speeding up Brainerd
I just got that message on slack let me
respond to it yes Oh guys okay we'll
work on some great stuff working on some
great stuff so oh I guess I'll tell you
guys what location D is we can talk
about this
sososo one my co-workers just PM me and
said is location to you on the phone
block by speaking of radar D oh I don't
know what this graph means but it looks
pretty you guys want to see it I don't
know what it means but let's look at it
so this is su stiffness compensation car
speed angle offset learner yeah we're
really trying to work on the open pilots
precision we're modeling tire stiffness
now if it location date is the Dayman
that's gonna run on the phone that's
going to do that ten centimeter
localization that we always talk about
Ranieri GPU is not practical so once we
have ten cent of your accurate
localization what's running location D
on the phone it's also going to do
calibration calibration does compensate
for y'all
calibration compensates for yaw and
pitch right now it doesn't compensate
for movement it doesn't compensate for X
movement or Y movement why does the
angle offset change
we'll come furtive Expo in the future
yeah yeah so we're gonna compensate
oh we're also going to compensate for
role we don't comment say for role right
now
drive that AI is completely subsisting
on hype nothing we do will kill drive
that AI only the world becoming smarter
will kill dry that AI and being able to
see through the bullshit how many miles
do we map we've mapped well 20 miles do
we have but we're really only mapping
the gray panda miles right now you will
get will get more when we're ready
really will really do the marketing
pushes first off you know so new Iran's
in the works new yarns new yarns many
years by neon today I baited icon a shot
like home daddy I by you
sorry I mean I don't mean to be really
chilly this is Sunday Skokie we don't
show that much oh if the road is bagged
it would show up an angle offset ah we
can we have the road Bank in location D
enroll
um there's no new me on it's the same
you lose any roles in if you buy any on
today it's the same you know yeah so
we're talking about the angle offset
letter which is like what angle you have
to put the we like to make the car go
straight why do I cancel all the hacks
because fuck hacks man they're so shitty
after the bug with that with the civic
steering I'm just not doing with them in
Turkey election today I know nothing
about that I don't know if they do
pepper thanks guys I just know that the
only place to the problem of politics is
the only way that anybody finds anything
out about politics is the media and the
media is a steaming shit pile yeah they
probably give that to an intern I
wouldn't I wouldn't quite say I'm sure
Karp at these only job was to do the
windshield wipers you could do a really
good job Mia hate the media growth now
look we as consumers need to demand a
better media media that doesn't lie to
us and doesn't spread fake news I mean
that's the thing like whammo as far as I
can tell has good technology but they're
either accidentally lying or
purposefully lying I'm not saying don't
go on the media wall
oh man even Ayn Rand took her social
security you know
Wow
well I was more successful recent Evo
Bloomberg oh I have my PR guy look into
that yes the only way media will change
is a preference changes it's true yeah
you got it yeah what's wrong with way mo
it's the disgusting advertising it's
just it's disgusting
um thoughts on must claimed full
autonomy released I don't think he said
that if he did say that it was bullshit
I think he said he's going to ship some
full autonomy features it who knows what
that means
bro this is not an energy drink it's
Lacroix water
it's literally carbonated water I don't
comment on crypto I'm not commenting on
crypto and I certainly don't talk about
security and then when you call comm a
level 3 when the statistics say that it
is yells will never be level 3 can I
talk about educate young scampi level 3
because I don't think the hardware is
reliable enough to get to level 3 I
don't think the hardware the only
hardware like when you look at GM
supercruise GM has redundant modules
redundant power supercruise maybe like
that architecture could get to level 3
but the EON powered by the car with one
can actuation thing will never get to
level 3 guys we got to be real about
that they'll always be level 2 future
hardware you know you incorporate the
same kind of stuff GM Julian chip agrees
and it also depends kind of how you
define level 3 Dulli on technology
that's right that's right
what level of this engagement is level 3
level 3 just means the manufacturer
takes liability sometimes why tall big
car companies think they need lidar
I'm not sure they really think that I'm
not sure why you think they think that I
think the media thinks self-driving cars
alright I'm not sure like who do you
talk to it a big car company right what
do I think of Udacity a I was driving
down a degree um again some of the
content is good any sort of degrees in
credentialism or absolute garbage I
don't know if that was a body I just
didn't answer the question the first
time I don't mind if you were ask them
if I don't answer them outside of us
maps working will be asked to death will
community tools be released to make maps
not from us will Tesla decreased or F
cheering well I hope so
I think Tesla should lower the torque on
their steering wheel and I think they
should also not disengage on steering
but I don't know I mean again they have
more data on this than I do I shouldn't
really say that's that's what I would do
I experience this is from my personal
experience in autopilot I thought that
that torque was to us all right I'm
gonna ban aetherium security guy I'm
certainly not talking about that house
mapping that uses a great badder
progressing quite good quite a lot quite
well alright maybe should we show you a
sneak peek of something should show you
this little peek
nano sneaky
[Music]
any plans for sensor fusion what do you
mean by that is he all saying yes what
are you saying yes - yeah I don't know I
wouldn't like don't have money for
credentials man that's all right
like you're not gonna don't don't here's
all I want you to say if you are not
already like a great programmer don't
expect to ever take one of those no this
thing now this thing feeds game no sneak
peek I just canceled it it's fine no
sneak peek I found some of the content
to be good their contents good it's
always what you get out of it - with all
of those online classes right I wouldn't
pay for content but I would uh ya know
stick because it's not ready yet
I'm just gonna show you what our
internal mapping stuff looks like that's
not ready if eon don't ever get pat yeah
i mean so how may i use the phone
company right um we're gonna release you
know just like phone companies new
generations of hardware every year and
we will continue to support that for as
long as apples of course their phones
right what's kinda messed up don't we
support new hardware every that we've
launched new hardware every year we're
phone company right I've never I've
never lied about this um say there are
no level three cars but they're never us
I mean they're just like yeah oh it's
messed up that the sneak peek was
canceled no well I'm terribly sorry but
I'm a liar and a hypocrite but at least
I'm not a liar about being a liar that's
right double we plug in I'm gonna plug
in my phone to charge oh you know what I
have to plug it in to charge
I'll plug it into this convenient Khmer
I can de oh yeah perfect watch like you
guys like the periscope just dies
is that gonna work oh no thing's gonna
work you got power cycles I know sounds
is this app I don't believe that sounds
broken
are you them no sound troll it's a
little annoying it's not going into that
now it's in the mode okay now it's in
fast charging mode okay do we plan to
support European cars no nope you're
looking at the cars we're gonna support
Hondas and Toyotas that's it
cup holder er no cup holder and we do
windshield mounts I can get into why but
you want it to be on the windshield the
cup holder the windshield is much more
rigidly attached to the car than the cup
holders well phone is this iPhone X best
one you can buy wow what a lovely Sunday
scope e today is a beautiful day kids go
outside don't make the mistake I did
don't start a company you could be
outside enjoying the sunshine riding on
an ATV you know I'm saying
oh yeah Acura Lexus yet supported to
periscope app is kind of trash fuck the
pixel to fuck Google get an iPhone X I
don't know he's high school - congrats
man
but Toyotas without a DSU were
supportive oh you mean like a a no we
don't own the off site you mean like the
Camry yeah does $2,000 bounty go support
the Camry yeah we're talking about the
heat we're talking about what to do
about it
we're aware I mean take the e on down
that's all we can really say like it's
not designed for that oh cool
coming by Jim is officially supported
but um well non-hybrid rav4 do stop and
don't know there's no reflash as they're
all canceled
well non hyperdrive for do stop and go
yeah you need toyou to pedal ricardo's
OG confluence Joe was talking about
external camera no no external camera no
okay okay are you the same guy was asked
about a theorem security they just look
crawl okay
it is literally water there's nothing
else in this shit there's like just
carbonation and water that's it it's
what let's see what's in here
ingredients carbonated water natural
flavor we don't compete with cruise
turns out our cars probably ready better
than you and accent why do we buy it if
it's just water because we like to show
off how rich we are calm my guys
absurdly rich by the way we have too
much money guys his natural that's a
great question any more details oh well
they have a phone number on the side you
can call for consumer information I mean
we could call them it has been what the
natural flavors literally made of carbon
and chemicals that's literally what my
brain is made of oh I have too much fun
you have too much of on guys have I
rented a model - yeah a bunch of times
I don't know well no tell so doesn't let
me buy their cars it's cool if I had a
phone right now but I wasn't talking to
you guys odd I would high class oh oh I
think I may have left my sunglasses you
know like I was gonna text you yeah this
girl after sunglasses
in my car last night huh no media advice
dude no I'm getting on board with this
ilan PewDiePie like that I've had it
with the media Alex if you're watching
this scope you right now
I found your sunglasses you're gonna
come by I'm here all day today if you
need them today or I'm here all week
next week because all I do is work
she didn't it wasn't a date she's a
friend of mine I think she actually just
left her sunglasses so we will we will
text her back after the scope is over yo
for a lovely hike and that's why my
necks fucked up look at that sunburn you
want to talk about what bad for you bros
yeah no work good that work his life
people all people around here we say
every people is the world overpopulated
no not all just drive through the middle
of America and don't realize how not
overpopulated the world is man no I
don't get burnt down I get fed up
sometimes with some shit I don't have
Twitter personally my name is Ivan Khmer
I well adding more miles help you get
sooner to fall autonomy who said we're
coming for full autonomy doesn't matter
the world's not overpopulated it's too
bad they put dumb people in charge of
shit but other than that the world no
the world just think about this guy's
everything you like in the world it
would be like every person you like in
the world there would be another one of
them if the world had EE as many people
right what security I do deep learning I
know about AI bros no I don't I don't
even do AI you know what I do I think
management of people that's right and
that's what happens man and you know
what they say I used when I was an
engineer I was good at my job but they
promote you just enough to the point
where you're in
right that's what they always say Kansas
is fake news I've been there
isn't there I think it's real I think I
think I've been to Kansas um you got
people skills guys people skills are all
that matters because let me tell you
something people are like you're gonna
like learn a lot of technical skills
like that's great but if you learn a lot
of people skills you could just
manipulate the sucker with technical
skills and to do it in to paint your
fence for you right this is a real skill
er
yeah Pied Piper broth don't take VC
funding um it was the best
entrepreneurial 21st century Elon Musk
you see he's crushing it and not only
that what he's doing is a cultural shift
right like when you compare that with
like Mark Zuckerberg Mark Zuckerberg is
not a cultural shift Mark Zuckerberg
represents the mainstream culture Google
represents the mainstream culture right
um the mint you've got like like
advertising is uh well Jeff Bezos is
pretty good as well um now Jeff Bezos
Jeff Bezos is is the execution man right
Amazon's did a phenomenal job executing
I should should I clean myself up a
little bit I didn't shower this morning
I showered yesterday before we got
massages last night I went at once had a
massage parlor it was nice normal
massages don't get any funny ideas and
then we went to shabu shabu bro you have
a shabu shabu thank you put the thing in
the pot you cook it and it's pretty good
ma'am nama shit entrepeneurial I said oh
maybe I got a chance
no Yong Yong it will never be level
three yeah that's another way of just
saying that you know we don't take
liability for anything you do with your
er never in the future that might change
but it will require new hardware when
are you going to China
someday bro soon before the next rap I
do put a song is out on my soundcloud
this morning any companies after comma
yeah you know once once you once you try
it once since you try it once you know
you'll end up doing it again so yeah
probably I think I already know what's
next but what's he'll calm ends up first
right it's a lot of work to still do are
you ever gonna make your own car someday
no it's bad business to be him there's
no reason you want to be in that
business unless your mission already
include something like electrical call
electric cars there's there's no reason
peripheral cameras we make er them to
two cameras they look at the road they
look at theirs most of your dis
engagements in open pilot are not being
caused and I say this all the time by
the lack of cameras they're being caused
by the poor software the software will
get better the hardware will have more
sensors and more processing right like
what is a phone hack think about a phone
right
it'll have what is it phone app right
everything we are literate commonly I is
literally making housing cheaper housing
could be so much cheaper if we you know
gave some if we fought I'll say politely
housing would be so much cheaper if we
found something else for the politicians
to do like imagine the politicians
everyday didn't go and politic they like
what's a non offensive thing for people
to do play video games political
simulator that's right if we could get
politicians we do want to add we latch
on cameras Oh we'll add more cameras I
will have more sensors we're cell phone
company they make better cell phone with
the more processing and the more sensors
in there right how do you assume the
data back from you users we use the cell
phone network and Wi-Fi and the internet
and all that good stuff but yeah if we
if we could get the politicians hooked
on political simulator then house it
would be incredibly cheap guys it would
all be super cheap
what if Apple tries to buy comma I like
Apple if Apple if Apple made a good
offer and they were gonna release the
product which would be very important to
me then yeah
I like Apple and Microsoft I think both
of these companies are they've been
around a long time
I like their cultural values
I don't think apples gonna sell either I
don't think they're gonna do that much
to be honest it's kind of sad like I
wish they would I'm psyched man I'd buy
an Apple car I've an iPhone X I love
this phone I have ear pods I have a
MacBook I love my Apple products like
they genuinely make my life better with
with really very little downside um you
know you think about like does Google
make my life better yes they do but
there's a huge downside to Google as
well Facebook got to the point where
they were just making my life worse so I
you know I quit Facebook and in 2012
Apple has never you know like okay I
have I had issue like I was switched to
android briefly like around the iPhone
five time but that was just cuz like
Apple wasn't offering large screens it's
not because they did anything bad I just
like didn't like their product up at
that time and I think they've turned it
around it made it better um dapples
doing a write with the keyboard guys
I like the keyboard mine hasn't
malfunction yet and they owned up to it
you know the Apple gets shit on it for
things that just are not things like
antenna gate Tesla is a very large
company Apple has a lot of money but I
don't see them buying Tesla Apple can
afford comma very easily oh now we're
not putting open power to other phones
Microsoft again my complaints about
Microsoft see my complaints about Google
are on the lines with Google's values
like I complained ok so here's something
here's something about Facebook right
like Instagram meters out the likes to
you right if you get 10 likes on
Instagram story they will slowly give
them to you they'll like trickle in the
like so you're more likely to check
Instagram I find that disgusting right
um but that's where Facebook is at odds
with their user when Microsoft releases
Windows XP I don't know if I would take
an acquisition off from Tesla actually
and we can and we can talk about why
that is I
think that what would happen if we did
get bought by Tesla is you would see a
huge huge se stalling of innovation in
the field I don't know much about
Richard Stallman 100 times it's not
selling out guys it's only selling out
if you compromise your values if you
sell the company to somebody who will
continue your values values are quite
aligned with Apple as I think I would
take a Microsoft acquisition offer -
again assuming they were gonna sell the
product I'm not sure our were that
aligned with Microsoft um but why do I
like Microsoft together because when
Microsoft makes something like Windows
XP it's buggy and crashes they don't
want to be buggy and crash we're on the
same side here right Microsoft and Apple
are on the side of their customers
whereas Google and Facebook
Tesla centralizing self-driving cars
well look if it wasn't for like us your
choice for a decent autonomy system
right now would be like autopilot or
supercruise and supercruise is not
really a scalable thing please issue
colic horns here for are you asking
about crypto criticizing my carbonated
drinks and you're asking me about
aetherium security criticizing my
carbonated water and asking for an IC
o---- oh if you're if your comment
didn't just disappear you'd be banned so
fast what books are you reading what am
i reading right now not that much sadly
reading rainbows end actually but slowly
very slowly I don't think I ever said I
would never sell I said I wouldn't sell
out there's a big difference right I am
still playing chess I'm still playing
chess I there's a big division selling a
company and selling out I've read I've
read deep learning book absolutely oh I
don't know I don't really consider like
that stuff reading I only consider like
when people ask like what are you
reading I think about like the fiction
I'm reading oh my friend did tell me my
friend did tell me about a blow and I
um you should shave Chesham twit
I am pathetically bad at chess and I'm
not enough of a twitch thought you know
if I was like maybe sex you're looking
maybe then I could stream chess even
given my low chest level but you know
yeah if it was nice I like them well got
a little carnal gets here or until an
hour whichever happens first special X
shoe I don't know what that is
you could have invented twitch so karma
raised their last round at 105 million
dollars so our current valuation is
probably a little bit above that I read
foundation back in the day very little
to modernist for my taste
105 million bras Nadia's are to use
Ubuntu I don't know arches too nerdy for
me
seems like arches for people who like
things to be difficult X monad any
foreseeable need for capital raise not
anytime soon we just raised 5 million
dollars it was easy to raise no guys you
don't want your evaluation to go up
didn't you watch HBO's Silicon Valley
you don't have a down round grows don't
want down rounds dual clamp versus
single point is that actually a problem
how can we share your successes if
common goes very successful not with a
fucking IC o---- scam scam scam scam
what's Manjaro I don't know what that is
gonna google it
oh man John Linux is a new Linux
distribution which is based on arch
linux I haven't heard about this I'm
reading about Manjaro guys how much you
run away do we have too long too long
too long I'm ready I'm ready to go to
sleep you know
now but our enemy is too long we can't
die we're like zombies but connect your
I invest in the mechanic and I lost
money that's right I bought the depth
and I lost money let me tell you what I
don't like about Manjaro they're calling
it 16 point oh eight is that natural or
are they just doing that to try to sound
like Ubuntu
oh not you ate this no no they've been
around for a while no no no no no no see
look at this shit 0.8.1 point three
fifteen point oh nine nothing I don't
like your marketing Manjaro I see what
you did there yeah I bought the dip bros
I thought it was gonna go back up
we're not updating the phone hardware no
new phones no new phones no no sorry I
dropped you guys um no hang on I should
kind of get ready the Carter's coming by
I should kind of get ready with some
stuff some some I'll tell you what it is
it's the new Honda Civic Tour quad that
actually works yeah that's that's
happening untitled not releasing panda
schematics oh yeah yeah there's a lot of
USB ports in the display we have a
contingency plan in case one place bites
the dust don't worry don't worry
but you guys already know the
contingency plan you guys read the code
you know you guys know what we're doing
it's not that much of a secret you
probably if you won't go back and look
at the old periscopes we've shown them
to you as well and we have a lot of that
but yes okay fine one new phone will be
supported in the probably the next
version of open bar right all right you
guys already know what it is I showed it
to you I went driving on the car and one
of the periscopes we do use eagle
actually yeah it's kind of getting
better since Autodesk bought them uh we
tried to run a casual competition once
they wanted to charge us like 75 grand
it was absurd um how did the accord
actuators compare to the Civic they're
shittier you want to wear camo well you
know I give me a job to come and I you
can apply on our website you know go to
come about a I cook job in the top bar
you can apply right there on lever we
use tensorflow
I don't know I don't really like
tensorflow
but it seems to be kind of more
supported I like the way packed which
thinks about things more but you know
tense flow came out first if someone
does reverse engineering or panda we
will sue you
we do have insurance yes absolutely we
have we have interns um no I'm not
really gonna sue you like if you post
the schematic I reverse engineered
schematic up and online and move that
cool Brown will sue people suing
people's bad I got two votes it's bad
don't sue people kids don't worry Oh
relax beautiful words nice Pleasant
mayor of San Francisco your charts
nothing Wow okay yeah bad Sony thoughts
of moving company back in New York not
gonna happen are your company's value of
5x higher in the Bay Area it's trouble
they did Studies drug is bad stay cool
guys are not on drugs
today I had a mop a and half cup coffee
I'm not really I'm over here the Civic
toward mod and if you sue me whatever
your name up there with Saudi know am i
buying a Tesla Roadster to point out no
I'm gonna fire the ml guy he's doing
well he's goes over West Coast though I
believe that the company value is not 76
percent me I'm the social media guy I'm
ml interns absolutely welcome I just do
the periscopes on the Twitter guys look
you think I actually write code anymore
I shit talk and I complain and I do that
sometimes publicly and sometimes
privately but ya know trust me you were
the guy behind the guy no no I wish man
a wish
and telling y'all the truth
the whole truth and nothing but the
truth so help me God I do mostly really
that's my job I should talk in
complaints I do read slam publicly on
Twitch check out twitch slim what's the
plan for after about 0.5 old pal 0.6
won't be a great this isn't it it's kind
of true if you had time for psychotic
that wasn't really the driverless what
would it be I would like to make my rap
better
we don't do remote I've never met it
snowed in no Google did away with don't
be evil see like they did away with it
because the humorless assholes were like
oh be good yeah you scare me a lot more
when you say be good not much let's talk
about the evil in the world
most of the evil in the world was not
done on the banner of don't be evil it
was done under the banner of be good
right Stan let's see rap God Summa LUMMA
dooma LUMMA you assuming i'm a human
where I got to do it again to you I'm
superhuman innovative and emitter
episode of anything I say is ricocheting
off of me Alam never stayed more than
ever devastate me had to give another I
cannot enter films because that
mayonnaise I've ever Elsa cuz I'm gonna
make a music you make elevator music oh
he's too mainstream that's what they do
make Jay get jealous they confuse it
that's hard with rap shot guy with dark
but I found a something music I don't
actually know the words
do I wanna lose yourself and make them
lose it
[Laughter]
come at ICON stand inside of the booth
truths filaments but true films until
two films come flying about if I mouths
now rewind it payback motherfucker for
the way that you doubted me how does it
taste
when I slept the taste out of your mouth
with a bass so loud that shakes the
place I'm Hannibal Lecter so just in
case you think of the saving face you're
gonna have no place to save at the time
I'm doing this place so Drake come AI n
okay well we'll show off one Khamenei I
had before we go
[Music]
I'll show you today this is all you need
to drive a car
[Music]